<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Mitch Beebe</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Mitch Beebe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Webscraping NHL Data with RSelenium, Part 2</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-15-webscraping-nhl-data-with-rselenium-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-15-webscraping-nhl-data-with-rselenium-part-2/</guid>
      <description>NHL-WHA merger With the absorption of four teams from the World Hockey Association in the 1979–1980 season, a new playoff system was introduced where 16 of the league’s 21 teams would qualify for postseason play. The four division winners would qualify for the playoffs while twelve wildcard positions rounded out the sixteen teams. At the beginning of each round the teams were seeded based on their regular season point totals, with the preliminary round being a best-of-five series while all other playoff series were best-of-seven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webscraping NHL Data with RSelenium, Part 1</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-08-rselenium-and-nhl-data-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-08-rselenium-and-nhl-data-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I love hockey. I also love data science. What’s better than merging the two and learn how to use RSelenium in the process?
A while ago, I wrote some web-scraping code to find the NHL standings as of Novermber 1st (roughly one month into the season). I was doing this in order to determine if a strong start to the season was related to end-of-season success. Fortunately, the website dropyourgloves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-07-hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-07-hello_world/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is my first post! This website was developed with R Markdown, Blogdown, Hugo, and served via Netlify. I tried hosting this on GitHub Pages, but had difficulty with Jekyll and the R Markdown format. Having read about Blogdown, I’m making the transition.
So far this is great. I can embed R code like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>